Guide to the Yale University Library Name/Title Card Catalog
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Nuevo Leon (Mexico: State). Governor (Box 5727)
- Nulaky, D.S. (Box 5728)
- Numismatische (Box 5729)
- Nunez Ramos, R. (Box 5730)
- Nunn, Thomas Percy (Box 5731)
- Nuremburg. Ordinances, etc. (Box 5732)
- Nutbrown maid (Box 5733)
- Nutzhorn (Box 5734)
- Nyberg, J. (Box 5735)
- Nylander (Box 5736)
- O. (Box 5737)
- O.H. (Box 5738)
- OPEC (Box 5739)
- O Smelom (Box 5740)
- Oakes (Box 5741)
- Oates, T. (Box 5742)
- Obedient rebels (Box 5743)
- Oberlin college (subject) (Box 5744)
- Objart (Box 5745)
- Obra dispersa (Box 5746)
- Obres completes (Box 5747)
- O'Brien, W. (Box 5748)
- Observations on the embargo (Box 5749)
- Obshcestvennoe nastroenie (Box 5750)
- O'Callaghan, J. (Box 5751)
- Occasional paper (Royal...) (Box 5752)
- Occasional papers on religion (Box 5753)
- Occupations unlimited (Box 5754)
- Ocherki (Box 5755)
- Ochi, H. (Box 5756)
- O'Connell (Box 5757)
- O'Connor, Rochelle (Box 5758)
- Oda, S. (Box 5759)
- Ode to (Box 5760)
- Odescalchi Collection (Box 5761)
- Odoevskij, V. (Box 5762)
- Odum, W.E. (Box 5763)
- Oeffnung nach Osten (Box 5764)
- Oeland (Box 5765)
- Oeser, E. (Box 5766)
- Oesterreichische Akademie der Wissenschaften. Kommission... M. (Box 5767)
- Oesterreichische Nationalbibliothek. Papyrussammlung. (Box 5768)
- Oesterreichs R. (Box 5769)
- Oezisik, M. (Box 5770)
- Offenbach (Box 5771)
- Official documents and (Box 5772)
- Oficio de leer (Box 5773)
- Ogawa, J. (Box 5774)
- Oggioni (Box 5775)
- Ogni s. (Box 5776)
- Oh! (Box 5777)
- Ohashi, S. (Box 5778)
- Ohio. Industry (Box 5779)
- Ohio Infantry (Box 5780)
- Ohio State University, Columbus. Graduate school (Box 5781)
- Ohnov (Box 5782)
- Oinaru (Box 5783)
- Oka, F. (Box 5784)
- Okamoto, Masafumi (Box 5785)
- Okayama ongaku (Box 5786)
- Okinawa (Box 5787)
- Oklahoma City school (Box 5788)
- Oktaba (Box 5789)
- Okuno, T. (Box 5790)
- Olbia (Box 5791)
- Old Dominion G. (Box 5792)
- Old masters and (Box 5793)
- Old times in (Box 5794)
- Oldfather, C. (Box 5795)
- Olecka (Box 5796)
- Oliphant, M. (Box 5797)
- Oliveira, K. (Box 5798)
- Oliver, Peter (Box 5799)
- Olivier, T. (Box 5800)
- Olmsted (Box 5801)
- Olsen (Box 5802)
- Olson, S. (Box 5803)
- Olympio (Box 5804)
- Omar (Box 5805)
- Omer, M. (Box 5806)
- Omotaka (Box 5807)
- On fiscal (Box 5808)
- On the American (Box 5809)
- On the rock (Box 5810)
- Onchi (Box 5811)
- One hundred flower (Box 5812)
- One titan (Box 5813)
- O'Neill, Eugene (continued) (Box 5814)
- Oneiro s. (Box 5815)
- Only by (Box 5816)
- Onomastic works (Box 5817)
- Ontario. Legislative Assembly. (Box 5818)
- Ontwerp (Box 5819)
- Oosterzee (Box 5820)
- Open skull. (Box 5821)
- Operational m. (Box 5822)
- Opinion letters (Box 5823)
- Oposicion a fondo (Box 5824)
- Oppenheim, Edward Phillips (continued) (Box 5825)
- Oppler (Box 5826)
- Optical spectra. (Box 5827)
- Or h. (Box 5828)
- Orange, France. (Box 5829)
- Orbea, Fernando de (Box 5830)
- Ordaz, G. (Box 5831)
- Orderly landscape (Box 5832)
- Ore dorot (Box 5833)
- Oregon. Secretary of State (Box 5834)
- Oregon State University. N. (Box 5835)
- Orfeo (Box 5836)
- Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (C) (Box 5837)
- Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (M) (Box 5838)
- Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (U) (Box 5839)
- Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development. Library (Box 5840)
- Organisation for European Economic Co-operation. Economic conditions in Italy (Box 5841)
- Organisnos (Box 5842)
- Organization of American States. General Secretariat (Box 5843)
- Organizational weapon (Box 5844)
- Oribatidae (Box 5845)
- Orientalische Bibliographie (Box 5846)
- Origenes de los vascos (Box 5847)
- Origines de Rome (Box 5848)
- Origo legum (Box 5849)
- Orleans (surname) (Box 5850)
- Orlovsky, D. (Box 5851)
- Orni, E. (Box 5852)
- Orphal (Box 5853)
- Ors (Box 5854)
- Ortega Munilla y... (Box 5855)
- Orthodox Eastern church. Liturgy and ritual (continued) (Box 5856)
- Ortiz (Box 5857)
- Orton (Box 5858)
- Orzeszkowa (Box 5859)
- Osaka kembutsu (Box 5860)
- Osborn, Frederick (Box 5861)
- Osborne, K. (Box 5862)
- Osgood, Cornelius (Box 5863)
- Osiander (Box 5864)
- Oslo. Nobel Institut (Box 5865)
- Osnovy b. (Box 5866)
- Osservatorio g. (Box 5867)
- Ostend (Box 5868)
- Ostlere (Box 5869)
- Ostrowski (Box 5870)
- Osvoenie kosmosa (Box 5871)
- Ota, Toju (Box 5872)
- Otero, M. (Box 5873)
- Otis, G. (Box 5874)
- Otruba, M. (Box 5875)
- Ottawa. F. (Box 5876)
- Otto III, Emperor of Germany, 980-1002 (Box 5877)
- Ottoman (Box 5878)
- Ou-yang, Hsiu (continued) (Box 5879)
- Oudot (Box 5880)
- Our empire (Box 5881)
- Our trees (Box 5882)
- Out west (Box 5883)
- Outlines of the principal... (Box 5884)
- Ovchinnikov, V.E. (Box 5885)
- Overhoff (Box 5886)
- Overton, J. (Box 5887)
- Ovid. Translations (Box 5888)
- Owa, I. (Box 5889)
- Owen, L. (Box 5890)
- Owens, W.A. (Box 5891)
- Oxford. English Cathedral (Box 5892)
- Oxford dictionary of the... (Box 5893)
- Oxford prize poems (Box 5894)
- Oxman, A. (Box 5895)
- Oz (Box 5896)
- Ozhegova, M.N. (Box 5897)
- P.A.F. (Box 5898)
- P.O. (Box 5899)
- Pa erh san chu (Box 5900)
- Pablo, M. (Box 5901)
- Pacheco, O. (Box 5902)
- Pacific explicator (Box 5903)
- Pacific science congress (Box 5904)
- Packard, J. (Box 5905)
- Padellaro, A. (Box 5906)
- Padrin, L. (Box 5907)
- Paetel, K. (Box 5908)
- Page, F. (Box 5909)
- Pageant (Box 5910)
- Paginas nacionales (Box 5911)
- Pai, Chue (Box 5912)
- Pai, R.B. (Box 5913)
- Pain (surname) (Box 5914)
- Paine, Thomas. Miscellaneous articles (Box 5915)
- Painting in the... (Box 5916)
- Pajaro, E. (Box 5917)
- Pakistan. Copyright Office (Box 5918)
- Pakistan story (Box 5919)
- Palacios (Box 5920)
- Palagi (Box 5921)
- Palazzi (Box 5922)
- Palec (Box 5923)
- Palestine and (Box 5924)
- Palgrave, G. (Box 5925)
- Palladio d. (Box 5926)
- Palm, T. (Box 5927)
- Palmer, D. (Box 5928)
- Palmer, M. (Box 5929)
- Palmerston (Box 5930)
- Paludan (Box 5931)
- Pamiatniki IUgo-Z. (Box 5932)
- Pamunkey (Box 5933)
- Pan (titles) (Box 5934)
- Panama. Direccion de Estadistica y Censo (continued) (Box 5935)
- Pan-American Institute of Geography and History. Commission on History (Box 5936)
- Pan-American Union. Department of Public Information (Box 5937)
- Panchatantra (Box 5938)
- Pandora's g. (Box 5939)
- Pangaud, C. (Box 5940)
- Panjab University (Box 5941)
- Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968 (continued) (Box 5942)
- Panstwo i... (Box 5943)
- Panu, A. (Box 5944)
- Pao-Pao (Box 5945)
- Papa no (Box 5946)
- Papazian, A. (Box 5947)
- Papers and letters (Box 5948)
- Papers on p. (Box 5949)
- Papon (Box 5950)
- Papyrus Harris no. 1 (Box 5951)
- Paracelsus, 1493-1541 (continued) (Box 5952)
- Paraguay. D. (Box 5953)
- Parana (Box 5954)
- Parda (Box 5955)
- Paredes, S. (Box 5956)
- Pareto, Vilfredo, 1848-1923 (continued) (Box 5957)
- Paris, Gaston (author) (Box 5958)
- Paris. Commune (Box 5959)
- Paris. Laws, statutes, etc. (Box 5960)
- Paris. Theatre V. (Box 5961)
- Pariset, E. (Box 5962)
- Park, Jason (Box 5963)
- Parker, D. (Box 5964)
- Parker, James (Box 5965)
- Parker, S. (Box 5966)
- Parkes, K. (Box 5967)
- Parks, F. (Box 5968)
- Parliamentary talk (Box 5969)
- Parnell (Box 5970)
- Parr, C. (Box 5971)
- Parrish, R. (Box 5972)
- Parsch, P. (Box 5973)
- Parsons, Robert (Box 5974)
- Partai S. (Box 5975)
- Parti des... (Box 5976)
- Partida, A. (Box 5977)
- Partido da... (Box 5978)
- Partidul Comunist Roman-History (Box 5979)
- Partisan's oath (Box 5980)
- Partito Popolare Italiano (Box 5981)
- Partridge, W. (Box 5982)
- Pasajera (Box 5983)
- Pascal, R. (Box 5984)
- Paseos coloniales (Box 5985)
- Pasos, C. (Box 5986)
- Passarge (Box 5987)
- Passion de V. (Box 5988)
- Past meridian (Box 5989)
- Pastoral da (Box 5990)
- Patanjali (Box 5991)
- Pateri, G. (Box 5992)
- Pathetic (Box 5993)
- Patmos (Box 5994)
- Patric (Box 5995)
- Patriotism (titles, etc.) (Box 5996)
- Patten (Box 5997)
- Patterson, C. (Box 5998)
- Pattison (Box 5999)
- Pauffin, Henry (Box 6000)
- Paul, D. (Box 6001)
- Paul-Dubois (Box 6002)
- Pauli, I. (Box 6003)
- Paulsen, Frederich (Box 6004)
- Paupe (Box 6005)
- Pavese, C.O. (Box 6006)
- Pavlov, V. (Box 6007)
- Pawson (Box 6008)
- Payne, F. (Box 6009)
- Pays (Box 6010)
- Paz Soldan, Mateo (Box 6011)
- Peabody Museum News (Box 6012)
- Peace research (Box 6013)
- Peake, J. (Box 6014)
- Pearl (Middle English poem) (Box 6015)
- Pearson, H. (Box 6016)
- Peasant sage (Box 6017)
- Pech, A. (Box 6018)
- Peck, T. (Box 6019)
- Peddie (Box 6020)
- Pedra, P. (Box 6021)
- Peeke, H. (Box 6022)
- Peet, W.S. (Box 6023)
- Pei cheng lu (Box 6024)
- Pei-ching ta (Box 6025)
- Pei Kai (Box 6026)
- Peile (Box 6027)
- Peiser (Box 6028)
- Peking leader (Box 6029)
- Pelham family (Box 6030)
- Pellegrini, M. (Box 6031)
- Pellisson, J.C. (Box 6032)
- Pemba, T. (Box 6033)
- Pen portraits (Box 6034)
- Pencheva (Box 6035)
- Peneau, Yves (Box 6036)
- P'eng, Po-shan (Box 6037)
- Penguin r. (Box 6038)
- Penn, William (author) (M) (Box 6039)
- Pennell, M. (Box 6040)
- Pennsylvania (state) (author) (Box 6041)
- Penn. Department of Mines (Box 6042)
- Penn. State Hospital (Box 6043)
- Pennsylvania infantry (Box 6044)
- Pennsylvania steel (Box 6045)
- Pensadores politicos (Box 6046)
- Pension L. (Box 6047)
- People (Box 6048)
- People's journal (Box 6049)
- Pepper (Box 6050)
- Per mare (Box 6051)
- Peraza (Box 6052)
- Percival, H.V.T. (Box 6053)
- Pere (Box 6054)
- Pereira, O. (Box 6055)
- Perer, B. (Box 6056)
- Perez, I. (Box 6057)
- Perez de Vargas (Box 6058)
- Perez-Remon, J. (Box 6059)
- Performance art (Box 6060)
- Peri K. (Box 6061)
- Periodicals that... (Box 6062)
- Perkins, D. (Box 6063)
- Perks, William (Box 6064)
- Permanent (Box 6065)
- Pernicone (Box 6066)
- Perottino, S. (Box 6067)
- Perrett (Box 6068)
- Perron, W. (Box 6069)
- Perry, G.M., 1862-1944 (Box 6070)
- Perry's pictorial (Box 6071)
- Persijn, J.P. (Box 6072)
- Personal effects (Box 6073)
- Personnel management c. (Box 6074)
- Perspectives on Brazilian (Box 6075)
- Perthes (Box 6076)
- Peru. Dirreccion General (Box 6077)
- Peru (Viceroyalty) (Box 6078)
- Pervago (Box 6079)
- Peschier (Box 6080)
- Pessoa, Francisco L. (Box 6081)
- Petain (Box 6082)
- Peter I, Emperor of Russia, 1672-1725 (continued) (Box 6083)
- Petera Stuckas (Box 6084)
- Peters, George H. (Box 6085)
- Petersburg Centennial (Box 6086)
- Peterson, Charles S. (Box 6087)
- Petersson, A. (Box 6088)
- Petit et n. (Box 6089)
- Petite illustration...Theatre [Nouvelle serie] no. 258. (Box 6090)
- Petofi, S. (Box 6091)
- Petrarca, Francesco, 1304-1374 (H) (Box 6092)
- Petri, P. (Box 6093)
- Petrographs (Box 6094)
- Petrov, Aleksandr K. (Box 6095)
- Petrovskii, V. (Box 6096)
- Petsche, J. (Box 6097)
- Petty (Box 6098)
- Peuser, Gunter (Box 6099)
- Peyton (Box 6100)
- Pfarl, Peter (Box 6101)
- Pfeiffer family (Box 6102)
- Pfleiderer, R. (Box 6103)
- Phaen ha (Box 6104)
- Phantom (Box 6105)
- Phelan, John (Box 6106)
- Phelps, William Lyon. R. (Box 6107)
- Phialas, Peter G. (Box 6108)
- Philadelphia. Library Company (Box 6109)
- Philadelphia Museum of Art (continued) (Box 6110)
- Philatelic Magazine (Box 6111)
- Philip, O. (Box 6112)
- Philippi, R. (Box 6113)
- Philippine press... (Box 6114)
- Philippines. Bureau of Energy... (Box 6115)
- Philippines. Department of the... (Box 6116)
- Philippines. Office of the Regional... (Box 6117)
- Philips (Box 6118)
- Phillips, Ali (Box 6119)
- Phillips, Henry (Box 6120)
- Phillips, R. (Box 6121)
- Phillips Collection (Box 6122)
- Philo, of Byblos (Titles cataloged after Dec. 1980) (Box 6123)
- Philoprotest (Box 6124)
- Philosophical transactions... (Box 6125)
- Philosophische L. (Box 6126)
- Philosophy of Plato (Box 6127)
- Phipson (Box 6128)
- Phonetische (Box 6129)
- Photographic image (Box 6130)
- Phra s. (Box 6131)
- Phuttharo (Box 6132)
- Physico-chemical (Box 6133)
- Physiological society (Box 6134)
- Pi, Chia-hsiang (Box 6135)
- Piacentini, D. (Box 6136)
- Piao chun (Box 6137)
- Pic, E. (Box 6138)
- Picasso, Pablo, 1881-1973 (continued) (Box 6139)
- Piccolino (Box 6140)
- Pickard, T. (Box 6141)
- Pickworth (Box 6142)
- Pictorial Hstory of the Thousand... (Box 6143)
- Pidgley (Box 6144)
- Pien che (Box 6145)
- Pierce (Box 6146)
- Pierne (Box 6147)
- Pierre C. (Box 6148)
- Pierz (Box 6149)
- Piettre, L. (Box 6150)
- Pignon (Box 6151)
- Pike, James S. (Box 6152)
- Pilgrim (titles, etc.) (Box 6153)
- Pille, H. (Box 6154)
- Pilsudski, Jozef, 1867-1935 (continued) (Box 6155)
- Pinacoteca T. (Box 6156)
- Pindar (Titles cataloged after Dec. 1980) (Box 6157)
- Pine Ridge T. (Box 6158)
- Ping ho (Box 6159)
- Pinillos (Box 6160)
- Pino Suarez, J. (Box 6161)
- Pinto, L. (Box 6162)
- Pioneer d. (Box 6163)
- Piotrowski, M. (Box 6164)
- Pipping, G. (Box 6165)
- Pirates de (Box 6166)
- Pirone, P. (Box 6167)
- Pisareva (Box 6168)
- Piso (Box 6169)
- Pitelis (Box 6170)
- Piton, M. (Box 6171)
- Pittenger (Box 6172)
- Pittsburgh steel (Box 6173)
- Pival, J. (Box 6174)
- Pla S. (Box 6175)
- Plaidoyer (Box 6176)
- Plan de d. (Box 6177)
- Planck, Max, 1858-1947 (continued) (Box 6178)
- Planning (Box 6179)
- Plans for reform (Box 6180)
- Plantet (Box 6181)
- Plat (Box 6182)
- Plato. Opera. English translation. Stennett (Box 6183)
- Plato. Republic (subject) (Box 6184)
- Plato (subject) (N) (Box 6185)
- Platoon (Box 6186)
- Plaut, L. (Box 6187)
- Playa f. (Box 6188)
- Plea (Box 6189)
- Plekhanov, N. (Box 6190)
- Plezia (Box 6191)
- Plisko (Box 6192)
- Plotinus (subject) (Box 6193)
- Plum (Box 6194)
- Pluralismus (Box 6195)
- Plutarchus (subject) (Box 6196)
- Po meci (Box 6197)
- Poblete Z. (Box 6198)
- Pocock, P. (Box 6199)
- Podkletnov (Box 6200)
- Poe, Edgar Allan, 1809-1849 (English notes) (Box 6201)
- Poellot (Box 6202)
- Poemes de la s. (Box 6203)
- Poems of the h. (Box 6204)
- Poesia de clase (Box 6205)
- Poesie da recita. (Box 6206)
- Poetas d. (Box 6207)
- Poeticheskii (Box 6208)
- Poetry of the transition (Box 6209)
- Poey, F. (Box 6210)
- Pogrebal'nye a. (Box 6211)
- Poiesis. (Box 6212)
- Poirson (Box 6213)
- Pokrovskii, N. (Box 6214)
- Poland. Archives... (Box 6215)
- Poland. Laws, statutes, etc. (Box 6216)
- Poland. Sejm-History (Box 6217)
- Pole (Box 6218)
- Poli, D. (Box 6219)
- Policy and practice (Box 6220)
- Poliquin (Box 6221)
- Politi, M. (Box 6222)
- Politica y e. (Box 6223)
- Political economy and p. (Box 6224)
- Political linkages (Box 6225)
- Political success (Box 6226)
- Politics and crime (Box 6227)
- Politics of conformity (Box 6228)
- Politics of upheaval (Box 6229)
- Politique et g. (Box 6230)
- Politus (Box 6231)
- Pollack, C. (Box 6232)
- Pollard, R. (Box 6233)
- Pollock, L. (Box 6234)
- Polonaski (Box 6235)
- Polska Akademia Nauk. Instytut F. (Box 6236)
- Polska Akademia Umiejetnosci. Komisja j. (Box 6237)
- Polskie R. (Box 6238)
- Polya, J. (Box 6239)
- Pomare IV, Queen (Box 6240)
- Pommier, L. (Box 6241)
- Ponce, G. (Box 6242)
- Poniatowska, E. (Box 6243)
- Pontanus, Johannes (Box 6244)
- Pontificia Universita (Box 6245)
- Poole (Box 6246)
- Poor cow (Box 6247)
- Pope, Alexander, 1688-1744 (Individual works) (Box 6248)
- Pope, Alexander, 1688-1744 (subject) (Box 6249)
- Pope-Hennessy, John W. (Box 6250)
- Popol, S. (Box 6251)
- Popovic, T. (Box 6252)
- Popular b. (Box 6253)
- Population Council. (Box 6254)
- Population reports... (Box 6255)
- Porch (Box 6256)
- Porphyry (Box 6257)
- Port Sheldon (Box 6258)
- Porter, Arthur K. (Box 6259)
- Porter, Gene (Stratton) (Box 6260)
- Porter, Richard E. (Box 6261)
- Portis (Box 6262)
- Porto Alegre, Brazil. P. (Box 6263)
- Portraits and s. (Box 6264)
- Portugal. Conselho (Box 6265)
- Portugal. P. (Box 6266)
- Poruks (Box 6267)
- Posebna izdanja (Srpska akademija nauka i umetnosti); knj. 517. (Box 6268)
- Position, Body (Box 6269)
- Posse, O. (Box 6270)
- Postal (Box 6271)
- Postman, L. (Box 6272)
- Poteau, V. (Box 6273)
- Potosi (Box 6274)
- Potter, J. (Box 6275)
- Potts (Box 6276)
- Poulet (Box 6277)
- Pound, Ezra Loomis, 1885-1972 (H) (Box 6278)
- Pounnya, N. (Box 6279)
- Poussin, N. (Box 6280)
- Povest' t. (Box 6281)
- Powell, F. (Box 6282)
- Powell, Thomas E. (Box 6283)
- Power j. (Box 6284)
- Powicke, J. (Box 6285)
- Poynter, J. (Box 6286)
- Pozza, N. (Box 6287)
- Prace l. (Box 6288)
- Practical detergent (Box 6289)
- Practising Law Institute. Duties (Box 6290)
- Pradine, M. (Box 6291)
- Praetorius (Box 6292)
- Prague, K. (Box 6293)
- Prajna Sagara... (Box 6294)
- Prando (Box 6295)
- Prasow (Box 6296)
- Pratt, Anne (Box 6297)
- Pratt Institute (Box 6298)
- Prawat l. (Box 6299)
- Prazsky h. (Box 6300)
- Precolumbiaans (Box 6301)
- Preface to the p. (Box 6302)
- Preibisch (Box 6303)
- Preliminary study of C. (Box 6304)
- Premio N. (Box 6305)
- Prentiss, Mrs. H. (Box 6306)
- Presbyterian Church-Missions (Box 6307)
- Presbyterian Church of England (Box 6308)
- Presence et m. (Box 6309)
- Preservation policies (Box 6310)
- Presley (Box 6311)
- Pressman (Box 6312)
- Preston, T. (Box 6313)
- Preuss (Box 6314)
- Prevet (Box 6315)
- Priapea (Box 6316)
- Price, J. (Box 6317)
- Price, W. (Box 6318)
- Prickard (Box 6319)
- Priestley, J. (Box 6320)
- Priestley, K. (Box 6321)
- Prima (Box 6322)
- El primer n. (Box 6323)
- Primrose (Box 6324)
- Prince society (Box 6325)
- Princeton University (author) (L) (Box 6326)
- Princip (Box 6327)
- Principles of macroeconomics (Box 6328)
- Prinsep (Box 6329)
- Prinzessin (Box 6330)
- Prishvin, Mikhail (Box 6331)
- Pritchard, N. (Box 6332)
- Private lives (Box 6333)
- Pro Colore (Box 6334)
- The problem of the... (Box 6335)
- Problematica della... (Box 6336)
- Problemes de l'art (Box 6337)
- Problems in analysis (Box 6338)
- Problems of war (Box 6339)
- Problemy s. (Box 6340)
- Proceedings of (Box 6341)
- Proceedings of the town (Box 6342)
- Processo penal (Box 6343)
- Proctor (Box 6344)
- Production b. (Box 6345)
- Profecia (Box 6346)
- Profile (Box 6347)
- Programa (Box 6348)
- Progress (titles, etc.) (Box 6349)
- Progressive (Box 6350)
- Project squid (Box 6351)
- Prokosch, Walther (Box 6352)
- Promise them... (Box 6353)
- Propertius, Sextus (Box 6354)
- Proposal (Box 6355)
- Prosadikter (Box 6356)
- Prospectus (Box 6357)
- Proteccionismo (Box 6358)
- Protestantische (Box 6359)
- Protracted game (Box 6360)
- Proust, Marcel (subject) (Box 6361)
- Provenzalische (Box 6362)
- Provincia de la (Box 6363)
- Proyart (Box 6364)
- Proyek pengabdian (Box 6365)
- Pruemm, Hans (Box 6366)
- Prussia. Oberlandesgerichte (Box 6367)
- Prynne, William (author) A declaration (Box 6368)
- Przeworska (Box 6369)
- Pseudo (Box 6370)
- Psychiatrie (Box 6371)
- Psychological monographs (Box 6372)
- Psychology and population (Box 6373)
- Psychoyos, Olga (Box 6374)
- Pu j. (Box 6375)
- Pubblicazione dei... (Box 6376)
- Public administration series: Bibliography; P-583 (Box 6377)
- Public b. (Box 6378)
- Public life (Box 6379)
- Public service commissions (Box 6380)
- Publicaciones de la Caja... (Box 6381)
- Publicaciones estadisticas (Box 6382)
- Publication of the economic... (Box 6383)
- Publications de la Faculte des sciences (Box 6384)
- Publications of the American Folklore Society (Box 6385)
- Publications scientifiques (Box 6386)
- Pucci, R. (Box 6387)
- Pueblo, Colorado (Box 6388)
- Puerto Rico. Bureau of the... (Box 6389)
- Pufendorf (Box 6390)
- Puguh (Box 6391)
- Pulci medievale (Box 6392)
- Puls (Box 6393)
- Punjab (India) (Box 6394)
- Puranas (continued) (Box 6395)
- Purdue University. Engineering experiment station (Box 6396)
- Puritan (Box 6397)
- Purton (Box 6398)
- Puschmann (Box 6399)
- Pushkin, Aleksandr S. (subject) (Box 6400)
- Pushkin (titles, phrases, etc.) (Box 6401)
- Puti (Box 6402)
- Putnam (titles, etc.) (Box 6403)
- Py (Box 6404)
- Pyncebeck (Box 6405)
- Qa (Box 6406)
- Qas (Box 6407)
- Qissat (Box 6408)
- Quaderni di Filmcritica (Box 6409)
- Quaife (Box 6410)
- Quand (Box 6411)
- Quantz (Box 6412)
- Quarterly economic review of British... (Box 6413)
- Quartz (Box 6414)
- Qudat (Box 6415)
- Quebec (Province). Department of Tourism... (Box 6416)
- Queen, Ellery (continued) (Box 6417)
- Queen Mother (Box 6418)
- Queensland (titles, etc.) (Box 6419)
- Quellen und forschungen zur (Box 6420)
- Quellenbuch (Box 6421)
- Querard (Box 6422)
- Quest for Sir... (Box 6423)
- Questions of (Box 6424)
- Quick, J. (Box 6425)
- Quillard (Box 6426)
- Quincy (titles, etc.) (Box 6427)
- Quintana (Box 6428)
- Quioc (Box 6429)
- Quivira (Box 6430)
- R. (Box 6431)
- R.H. (Box 6432)
- Raa, F. (Box 6433)
- Rabb (Box 6434)
- Rabelais, Francois, 1490-1553? (subject) (L) (Box 6435)
- Rabinow, S.J. (Box 6436)
- Rabus (Box 6437)
- Racelis (Box 6438)
- Racine, Jean Baptiste, 1639-1699 (Individual works) (E) (Box 6439)
- Racovita (Box 6440)
- Radcliffe College. Women's... (Box 6441)
- Radford, William C. (Box 6442)
- Radice (Box 6443)
- Radiography (Box 6444)
- Radomir (Box 6445)
- Rae, J. (Box 6446)
- Raffaele, J. (Box 6447)
- Ragbag (Box 6448)
- Raguenet (Box 6449)
- Rahner, K. (Box 6450)
- Rail (Box 6451)
- Raimund, G. (Box 6452)
- Rainibe (Box 6453)
- Raja (Box 6454)
- Rajna, P. (Box 6455)
- Rakugo (Box 6456)
- Ralph Runnion (Box 6457)
- Ramadeva (Box 6458)
- Ramasar (Box 6459)
- Ramdun (Box 6460)
- Ramirez Diaz, L. (Box 6461)
- Ramos (Box 6462)
- Rampton (Box 6463)
- Ramsey, J. (Box 6464)
- Rances (Box 6465)
- Rand Corporation. Research memorandum (Box 6466)
- Rand note (continued) (Box 6467)
- Randegger (Box 6468)
- Randsborg (Box 6469)
- Rangwane (Box 6470)
- Rankokai (Box 6471)
- Rantoul (Box 6472)
- Raparini (Box 6473)
- Rapid i. (Box 6474)
- Rapperswyl (Box 6475)
- Rare people (Box 6476)
- Rashi (Box 6477)
- Rasmussen (Box 6478)
- Rasser (Box 6479)
- Ratchnevsky (Box 6480)
- Rathje (Box 6481)
- Ratner, S. (Box 6482)
- Rau, K. (Box 6483)
- Raun, G. (Box 6484)
- Ravailhe (Box 6485)
- Ravero (Box 6486)
- Rawley (Box 6487)
- Ray, G. (Box 6488)
- Raya, S. (Box 6489)
- Raymond de M. (Box 6490)
- Razafimahery (Box 6491)
- Razvitie e. (Box 6492)
- Reactions of s. (Box 6493)
- Read, T. (Box 6494)
- Reading Abbey (Box 6495)
- Readings in social security (Box 6496)
- Real and Ideal (Box 6497)
- Realidade educacional (Box 6498)
- Reason (titles, etc.) (Box 6499)
- Rebecca (Box 6500)
- Rebora, J. (Box 6501)
- Recent developments in... (Box 6502)
- Recherche sur les m. (Box 6503)
- Recht (Box 6504)
- Recke, Ernst (Box 6505)
- Reconnaissance de la... (Box 6506)
- Records of civilization (Box 6507)
- Recueil d'etudes romanes (Box 6508)
- Recuerdos de la Republica... (Box 6509)
- Red ice (Box 6510)
- Reddington (Box 6511)
- Redford (Box 6512)
- Redmond-Howard (Box 6513)
- Reed, Alfred (Box 6514)
- Reed, John S. (Box 6515)
- Reef (Box 6516)
- Reese, L. (Box 6517)
- Reeves, W. (Box 6518)
- Reflections of biologic... (Box 6519)
- Reform anticipated (Box 6520)
- Reformed church (Box 6521)
- Refugie (Box 6522)
- Regensburg (Box 6523)
- Regime p. (Box 6524)
- Regional development guide (Box 6525)
- Regional science symposium (Box 6526)
- Register of the parish... (Box 6527)
- Regnier, Henri de. Episodes (Box 6528)
- Regulations (Box 6529)
- Rei no... (Box 6530)
- Reiche (Box 6531)
- Reichner (Box 6532)
- Reid, F. (Box 6533)
- Reid, William (Box 6534)
- Reihe R. (Box 6535)
- Reimb (Box 6536)
- Reindorff (Box 6537)
- Reinhardt, H. (Box 6538)
- Reinold, E. (Box 6539)
- Reisen (Box 6540)
- Reiter, J. (Box 6541)
- Reker (Box 6542)
- Relacion historica... (Box 6543)
- Relations l. (Box 6544)
- Relief (Box 6545)
- Religion in B. (Box 6546)
- Religious conflict (Box 6547)
- Rem (Box 6548)
- Remarks upon the (Box 6549)
- Remembered past (Box 6550)
- Remion, J. M. (Box 6551)
- Remusat (Box 6552)
- Renan (Box 6553)
- Renaudin, L. (Box 6554)
- Rendle (Box 6555)
- Renich (Box 6556)
- Renoir, J. (Box 6557)
- Rentsch (Box 6558)
- Repertoire (Box 6559)
- Repertorio b. (Box 6560)
- Reponse des (Box 6561)
- Report of the Department (Box 6562)
- Report on the census of e. (Box 6563)
- Reports, analyses (Box 6564)
- Representations of r. (Box 6565)
- Republic of technology (Box 6566)